question_data = [
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "When you cry in space, your tears stick to your face.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "You can legally drink alcohol while driving in Mississippi.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "Nutella is produced by the German company Ferrero.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "Bulls are attracted to the color red.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "Vietnam's national flag is a red star in front of a yellow background.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "Video streaming website YouTube was purchased in it's entirety by Facebook "
                    "for US$1.65 billion in stock.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "French is an official language in Canada.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "The Lego Group was founded in 1932.",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "Slovakia is a member of European Union-",
        "correct_answer": "True",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "False"
        ]
    },
    {
        "type": "boolean",
        "difficulty": "easy",
        "category": "General Knowledge",
        "question": "Di-hydrogen Monoxide was banned due to health risks after being discovered "
                    "in 1983 inside swimming pools and drinking water.",
        "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": [
            "True"
        ]
    }
]
